{
    "subject": "resource/John_Hennessy_Saul",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "John Hennessy Saul (December 25, 1819-May 11, 1897) was a prominent horticulturist and landscape architect who assisted in the planning and the development of the National Mall in Washington D.C. and served as the first Chairman of Washington D.C.\u2019s Parks commission.",
    "human_readable": "John Hennessy Saul's comment is John Hennessy Saul (December 25, 1819- May 11, 1897) was a prominent horticulturist and landscape architect who assisted in the planning and development of the National Mall in Washington D.C. and served as the first Chairman of Washington D.C.'s Parks commission.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9088507890701294,
            "question": "What role did John Hennessy Saul hold in Washington D.C.'s Parks commission?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8902339935302734,
            "question": "Describe John Hennessy Saul's contributions to Washington D.C."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8859907388687134,
            "question": "In what year did John Hennessy Saul begin his work on the National Mall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8486964106559753,
            "question": "What significant project did John Hennessy Saul assist with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8369852900505066,
            "question": "What position did John Hennessy Saul hold in the Parks commission?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.809902012348175,
            "question": "What was John Hennessy Saul's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8074212670326233,
            "question": "When was John Hennessy Saul born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8024210929870605,
            "question": "What city was John Hennessy Saul associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7842245697975159,
            "question": "What field contributed to John Hennessy Saul's prominence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6569125056266785,
            "question": "When did John Hennessy Saul pass away?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=John Hennessy Saul's comment is John Hennessy Saul (December 25, 1819- May 11, 1897) was a prominent horticulturist and landscape architect who assisted in the planning and development of the National Mall in Washington D.C. and served as the first Chairman of Washington D.C.'s Parks commission.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1309_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field contributed to John Hennessy Saul's prominence?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1309_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city was John Hennessy Saul associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1309_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was John Hennessy Saul born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1309_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1309_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1309_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1309_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1309_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1309_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1309_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1309_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1309_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1309_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1309_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention John Hennessy Saul's involvement in the planning and development of the National Mall in Washington D.C. and his role as the first Chairman of Washington D.C.'s Parks commission, which aligns with the provided statement about him."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided information supports that John Hennessy Saul was a prominent horticulturist and landscape architect who assisted in the planning and development of the National Mall in Washington D.C. and served as the first Chairman of Washington D.C.\u2019s Parks commission."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}